VINCENT NOLAN

Carnacalla
Kilrush
Co. Clare.

8 085 251 9996

vincenolan999@yahoo.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly responsible and disciplined police officer with Fifteen Years Experience in a busy London borough having specialized in response and neighbourhood policing. Versed in meticulous attention to detail operating in high pressure environments, dedicated and personable approach to people. Experience in Dispute resolution, Recording and investigating incidents and preparing relevant documents for court and other multi-agencies.

QUALITIES/SKILLS

- Strong organisational skills with the ability to coordinate people and resources with compelling results.
- Resilient and adaptable with a positive approach to work.
- I take personal responsibility, with the competence to respond logically and decisively in difficult situations.
- Experienced in leading and developing a team.
- Exceptional communication skills.
- Clean driving record.
- First aid trained.
- GAA Football Coaching.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

• Continual professional development throughout service as a police officer with courses such as investigative skills, new recruit training and mentoring, workplace change management, health and safety, advanced first aid, advanced police driving.

EDUCATION

2004 Police Professional Training

Eighteen weeks residential training incorporating law, police powers, diversity, transparency and leadership.

Third Level

2002 The Mortgage Advice Qualification (MAQ) at The Chartered Insurance Institute. London

1998 Financial Planning Certificate (1-3) at The Chartered Insurance Institute, London.

Second Level

1990 11 GCSE passes incl. English, Maths, Physics, Business Studies at Barking Abbey High School, Barking, London.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Police Officer Metropolitan Police, London, UK.	March 2004 to date
Independent Financial Advisor and Mortgage Broker Progressive Financial Solutions	June 2003 – Mar 2004
Independent Financial Advisor and Mortgage Broker Zurich London, UK	June 2001 – June 2003
<u>Financial Advisor</u> Royal London Insurance, London, UK	June 1996 – June 2001
<u>Supervisor</u> Natwest Bank London, UK.	June 1990 – June 1996

REFERENCES

References available upon request